https://transwestair.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Transwest Air does not automatically collect personal and confidential information on the people who visit the Transwest Air Website. Here's how we handle the information we receive:
Information Collected and Stored Automatically
Every time you visit, we automatically store information on what Web browser you are using, what pages you are accessing, the date and time, and what site you came from. However, we don't know who you are. This type of information is used to identify trends and plan upgrades to the Website. For example, if we notice a section of the site rarely gets visited, we may pull the material, or re-work it to make it more useful to visitors.
Personal Information
You may choose to provide us with personal information. For example, you may send us an e-mail that would identify you, or send personal details to a Transwest Air staff member. Such communications are governed by the same policy as any other conversation; that is, they are considered private and confidential. We will not release any of your personal information unless you specifically tell us to do so.
Google Analytics
Google Analytics mainly uses first-party cookies to report on visitor interactions on this website. These cookies are used to store non-personally identifiable information. Browsers do not share first-party cookies across domains.
We are using Google Analytics for Display Advertisers feature, this third-party DoubleClick cookie is used to enable features, such as remarketing for products like AdWords on the Google Display Network. For more information about this cookie, visit the Google Advertising Privacy FAQ.
Google's aim is to show you relevant ads based on your interests. It feeds you ads related to your interests. You may control the types of ads you see by going to Google Ads Settings. There you can edit information or opt completely out of receiving interest based ads on Google.
If you don't want any of your data collected by Google Analytics from this site and any other participating sites, simply visit the Google Analytics opt-out page and install the add-on for your browser.
Book
Schedules
Services
Help Center
About Us
What’s New
Careers
Agent Log-in
Subscribe to our newsletter:
Email Address *
Follow us on Facebook
Learn more about our parent company:
